{
    "id": "30d62bfddb6147aa9149262c4433de12",
    "title": "By And Until | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will keep asking …………………. you send my payment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9127e9780d904d99aa2b0ccccb091273"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shop is open ...................... 9 pm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e154eff406f44fa18f9b4bee672b2e0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "They said that they would finish the job …………………. Friday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b07f9f21880465f9d7b35e58a2997c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for him ……………….. 12 o’clock and then I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ffc860034d3427e95ec580585661c4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be staying in this city ………………… the end of this month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a17560abe994a9196d1c98c0bd72bc5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be home …………………. five o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f23c3d39aeb54377b5c8ed496217227d"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. the end of the party, everybody was drunk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "By",
                "Until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35c974896c0a4f80a8a57bdd77c2c919"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be in bed ……………….. the time you get home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a8914dfe9b5f4e558cfbf2763f45f941"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be ready ………………… the time you arrive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0aed117cfe234622a5b3b7aa9da963d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will wait here …………………. you come back.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24e4126a7fa443568457f119dac1f8f5"
        }
    ]
}